# Ryan McKelvey

I am a passionate 24 year old software developer, with a wide range of skills that cover anything from back-end development to front-end design. I would consider myself a fast learning and adaptable person, who can work well in either self-driven or teamwork based projects. I would consider my biggest strengths to be in back-end development, and software testing/quality control. When I'm not at the computer, I enjoy film, and going hiking.

9 Northcourt, Wine Street, Sligo, Co. Sligo (+353)083 487 8397 ryanmckelvey98@gmail.com github.com/ryanmckelvey ryanmckelvey.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Tata Consultancy Services, Letterkenny — AWS Developer

SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

I am currently working at TCS as a part of the Cloud Computing team, I am working primarily with Amazon Web Services and working towards certifications with the help of TCS. I am also learning to work with Microsoft Azure and Google Cloud Platform

#### **Clanwilliam Health, Sligo** — *Customer Support Executive*

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

During my time with Clanwilliam Health, I helped users with various IT issues and created tickets from calls, working with my team to resolve them.

#### Software Development Tutor, Sligo

MAY 2020 - PRESENT

I am currently giving lessons in software development to students at Sligo IT, who require help with their modules.

#### **Pramerica**, Letterkenny — Associate Systems Developer

APRIL 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

During my time at Pramerica, I primarily worked on developing an in-house tool for hardware asset management.

### LANGUAGES AND FRAMEWORKS

.NET (Core, UWP)

Python (Django, Flask,

Sci-Kit)

**Angular** 

HTML/CSS

SOL

**GOLang** 

#### **SKILLS**

**AWS** 

**Machine Learning** 

**Full Stack Development** 

**Agile** 

**SDLC** 

Testing / TDD

**Object Oriented Design** 

Teamwork

Communication

**Problem Solving** 

#### **EDUCATION**

## ITSligo, Sligo — BSc Hons Computing in Software Development

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2020

Second Class Honours, Grade 1 (2:1)